

CLAIRE JOY C.

ABEQUIBEL

Profile

A risk taker, flexible and quick learner. Experiences in handling clients by creating a web design, logos, banners had led to a versatile skillsets. Can handle criticism without feeling so discourage and use it as an opportunity to improve. Can adjust to different situations and can follow orders with minimal supervision.

Contact

29 Opal St. San Antonio CAA Las Pinas City, 1740

0905-277-5813

Projects

abeq_claire@yahoo.com

behance.net/clarasophitia

Employment History

AFFINITY EXPRESS I WEB DESIGNER

UP-AyalaLand Technohub, Quezon City

n City

Develop and maintains web documents and site templates using agreed upon tools, tag libraries, coding standars & validation tests.

Manages the architectural design and structure of the page layout and navigation.

CIRCUS CO. LTD I WEB DESIGNER

AUG 2013 - OCT 2014

OCT 2014 - MAY 2016

The Enterprise Center, Ayala Avenue, Makati City

Focus on designing a site that promotes a company's business, branding and logo.

Design and develop the overall look of a website Reflect on the aesthetic of the site by considering color & typography.

IT CRAFT SYSTEMS INC I INTERN

FEB 2013 - MAY 2013

Madrigal Business Park Alabang, Muntinlupa City

Take projects from specification to end user experience.

Assist an on-going project of a Web Developer Team.

Education

AMA COMPUTER COLLEGE - LAS PINAS

MAY 2009 - APR 2014

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

JESUS REIGNS CHRISTIAN COLLEGE

JUN 2007 - APR 2009

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

BERNARDO COLLEGE

JUN 2002 - MAR 2006

High School | Pulanglupa Las Pinas City

Skills

kahokou-cl.com cafe-and-bar-mori1026.com kidsroom-nonnon.com s-daishi.com lauberge-shibata.jp shinjouji.jp

Photoshop							\bigcirc	\subset
llustrator							\bigcirc	\subset
Dreamweaver				\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\subset
Javascript			\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	C
HTML							\bigcirc	\subset
CSS					\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\subset
PHP			\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	C
mySQL			\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\subset
Visual Basic				\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\subset
Bootstrap				\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	\bigcirc	C